(soft upbeat music)
♪ I thought I saw a man brought to life ♪
♪ He was warm, he came around
like he was dignified ♪
♪ He showed me what it was to cry ♪
♪ Well, you couldn't be
that man that I adored ♪
♪ You don't seem to know ♪
♪ Or seem to care what your heart is for ♪
♪ I don't know him anymore ♪
♪ There's nothin' where he used to lie ♪
♪ Our conversation has run dry ♪
♪ That's what's goin' on ♪
♪ Nothing's fine, I'm torn ♪
♪ I'm all out of faith,
this is how I feel ♪
♪ I'm cold and I am shamed ♪
♪ Lying naked on the floor ♪
♪ Illusion never changed ♪
♪ Into something real ♪
♪ I'm wide awake and I can
see the perfect sky is torn ♪
♪ You're a little late ♪
♪ I'm already torn ♪
♪ So I guess the fortune teller's right ♪
♪ Should have seen just what was there ♪
♪ And not some holy light ♪
♪ But you crawled beneath
my veins and now ♪
♪ I don't care, I have no luck ♪
♪ I don't miss it all that much ♪
♪ There's just so many things ♪
♪ That I can't touch, I'm torn ♪
♪ I'm all out of faith,
this is how I feel ♪
♪ I'm cold and I am shamed ♪
♪ Lying naked on the floor ♪
♪ Illusion never changed ♪
♪ Into something real ♪
♪ I'm wide awake and I can
see the perfect sky is torn ♪
♪ You're a little late ♪
♪ I'm already torn ♪
♪ Torn ♪
♪ There's nothing where he used to lie ♪
♪ My inspiration has run dry ♪
♪ That's what's goin' on ♪
♪ Nothing's right, I'm torn ♪
♪ I'm all out of faith ♪
♪ This is how I feel ♪
♪ I'm cold and I am shamed ♪
♪ Lying naked on the floor ♪
♪ Illusion never changed ♪
♪ Into something real ♪
♪ I'm wide awake and I can
see the perfect sky is torn ♪
♪ I'm all out of faith ♪
♪ This is how I feel ♪
♪ I'm cold and I am ashamed ♪
♪ Bound and broken on the floor ♪
♪ You're a little late ♪
♪ I'm already torn ♪
♪ Torn ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Oh yeah, oh yeah ♪